This love in my heart,
it will burn on forever.
Granting me courage, I
hope it will never stop.
No matter where you
are, nothing is too far.
With our everlasting bones,
we'll reach it, we are home.
I'm
so truly grateful.
I ran into you on that day so long ago.
We laughed every moment
with tears in our eyes.
Till we knew we weren't alone.
The blowing wind came in
and joined us on our way.
And with it I know we'll rise.
We'll be flying up high.
Why, tell me why are you giving up?
Why, tell me why you wanna fight alone?
Hey, what kind of future
do you think you have?
Your dream is already in your hands.
This love in my heart,
it will burn off forever.
Granting me courage, I
hope it will never stop.
I don't matter where you
are, nothing is too far.
With our everlasting
plans, we'll reach it.
We are home from the horizon,
out on the edge of the world.
If there is a place that
I'd want to take you to?
Let's head for it then!
But as for the way we already know.
We promised it long ago.
You scream by your voice.
That can't break through the silence.
Feeling defeated.
It crushes your helpless heart.
I've got your back, I swear.
I'll always be here.
Let's put our fate within
this light under the sun.
Can you close your eyes and
just listen to my voice?
Let's find the answer together.
I'm telling you in our path.
I trust that it will lead us.
To another sea untarded.
Cause now we are home.
On the horizon, out on
the edge of the world.
There is a place I want to take you to.
Let's head for it then.
But after the way we already know.
We promised it long ago.
You insolent brat.
Gaze upon my sword with fear!
It's quite splendid, isn't it?
Best remember the name Pretzel You're
seeing a one-of-a-kind masterpiece
It's going to teach you a lesson On
how we run things in the new world
Huh?
How can you call it one of a kind?
Aren't you holding six of them?
Let's get out of here, Luffy.
It's not over.
Let's go!
Third gear!
Now!
Gum-Gum!
All of them run!
You don't know what you've
gotten into, pathetic.
That's all!
No!
That's my brother.
Luffy.
Oh no, don't forget they work for Big Mom.
We really shouldn't take this lightly.
I'm surprised even Luffy's
having a hard time.
Hurry, get up!
What now?
Not so fast, little missy.
I'm still here.
Remember, you can't retreat.
Heat.
Your heart must be pounding in
your throat by now, poor thing.
Worst generation, huh?
I say, whoop-de-doo!
Hope you all had a good time playing
pirates cruising the Grand Line.
I've seen countless faces of
underlings like you come and go,
always spouting the same nonsense that
their captain will be king of the pirates.
You know how that story ends? In despair.
You all wander into Mama's
territory and learn the same lesson.
Captain Kid did.
Also, Roar of the Sea, Apu, Gang
Buggy, and even Mad Monk-Aruge.
Only Buggy recognized the danger.
He had enough wits about
him to join forces with us.
The rest of those pathetic
worst-generation upstarts
were driven away without even
catching a glimpse of Mama.
Well, one of them had some backbone.
That's Mad Monk-Aruge.
The scoundrel was crafty enough to take
down one of our strongest officers.
Hard to believe they were the sweet
four generals not so long ago.
That's as far as he made it.
Mama was so furious she sent
brother Cracker to finish the job.
Your friend has nowhere to run.
I imagine he must be taking
his last breath by now?
She's gone.
Listen closely.
You've reached your final
stop in the new world.
You want to fight an
emperor? Really? You fool.
You won't even get close to Mama.
Infiltrating the tea party,
stopping the wedding,
and then walking out of here
alive with your lost Gourmet.
Oh, yeah, like that's
ever going to happen.
This forest will be your final resting
place without ever catching sight of Mama.
No, my climb attacked!
Welcome to Mirror World.
You're going to love it here.
Stop it! Let me go!
Come on. Come on!
Come to old Barrel.
I can't wait to carve up that little
face in the comfort of another dimension.
Bound! Help me!
Just give in already.
Let her go, Barrel!
Thanks a bunch.
Are you serious?
Nice going, Pound.
You just committed treason against Mama.
You're dead to us.
And soon, just dead.
Here comes a thunderbolt tempo!
She'll be back as always, huh, well?
You see, her ability lets her appear
pretty much any place that has a mirror.
Sorry, are you in trouble now?
Apparently, I was already in trouble.
Cracker was told to kill me
by none other than Lin-Lin.
Oh, yeah, it just reminded me.
Are you one of Lola's friends, by chance?
Uh-huh.
I would say that officially
settles it, then.
Lola's mother has to be Big Mom.
The fact that the creatures here have such
a reaction to this is proof in itself.
I'll make sure to put
it to good use, Lola.
Oh no!
We're in his pathway!
Hey, hold on!
Don't forget we still have a duty
to uphold us the seducing ones!
We can't let anyone escape!
Right!
Plunk is back!
Come on, Kong!
God, my God!
Hard biscuit block!
No good!
Dear guy!
He's using armament Haki!
If you truly care about Vinsmok Sanji as
a friend, surely you should let him go.
He is the prince of a mighty kingdom.
His status far exceeds your own, boy.
By taking a noble wife,
he can enjoy living in luxury
with every desire catered to.
Would you rather selfishly
take your friend back or
allow him to partake in the
happiness he is entitled to?
Compared to his new family,
you're childish and weak.
Can you imagine what a prince would
say looking upon a failure like you?
Get out of my sight, you
wretched low-class pirate!
Karoo!
Karoo! Karoo!
Karoo! Muscle balloon! Let's go!
Ha! Ha!
Fourth gear!
Bounce man!
Muscle Balloon isn't a bad name
coming from a simpleton like you.
But bouncing balls don't exactly
strike fear into my heart.
Let me spell it out one more time.
You're low class.
Go home already!
All right, gum, gum, gum!
Hard biscuit block!
Gah! Gah!
General Cracker!
You don't know Sanji at all!
You insult him, even if he is happy with
his new life and doesn't want to come back!
He'd never talk to us like that!
No, it's not!
Not until I save Sanji!
All right, Kong Kong!
I wouldn't push your luck with me.
Come here!
Kong Kong!
Let's all roll!
General Prattler!
I'll admit that impressed me.
Well done!
Breaking my armor?
And just who are you?
Is that not obvious?
Pretty sure I already introduced myself
as the Sweet Three General Cracker.
That was my favorite armor,
you know. Armor? Liar!
I saw him cough up blood!
That was jam.
I'm a true craftsman at heart.
It even tasted good, too.
After consuming the bis-bis
fruit, I became a biscuit man.
I make infinite amounts of
biscuits and manipulate them.
The possibilities are endless.
Crushed biscuit!
If I can imagine it, I can craft it.
Look familiar, the face
of a hardened warrior.
Much like biscuits through history,
they change shapes based on the
era or the whims of their creator.
Not many people have ever caught
a glimpse of my true self.
Have you seen my wanted poster
that's issued by the government?
That's not my face.
It's my armor.
Frankly, I detest the feeling of pain.
And the same goes for injections.
That's why I surround myself in a suit of
armor and control it to fight in my stead.
It multiplies as I clap.
This is the height of artisanal biscuitry.
A dream come true.
Limitless forces at my disposal!
The one you struggled
so hard to destroy was
but a single biscuit
warrior in a line of many.
I can duplicate them as
many times as I desire.
Now do you understand why you will
never see Vinsmoke Sanji again?
I'll be back.
I'm gonna see Soji! You're wrong!
Truth is, no matter how strong you are,
there are people out
there you can never beat.
Learning to accept that
doesn't mean you've failed.
It's progress.
You still want to fight?
AAAAAAHHHHHHHHHHH!!!
We can't stick around here!
We don't get a chad, noooooooooo!
Hopefully we'll be safe now.
There's really no point
in us sticking around.
Oh, I'm still here.
We can't escape!
You could try it, but
there will be consequences!
I thought I told you all to
help out Luffy with Cracker!
No matter how many of you wither,
it won't bother me one bit!
How could you say something
that awful with a smile?
So you're afraid of General Cracker?
Well, how about Big Mom, then?
Which one is scarier?
You are!
I get it now.
Am I smarter or what? Here, listen.
Listen, I got this all figured out.
From this point on, you can call
me your Big Bro Chopper, okay?
Sure, no problem.
Cool.
Okay, so what's the thing you figured out?
My Cho-Bro, your Cho-Bro.
Yeah, it's short for Big
Bro Chopper. Cho-Bro.
I guess that's okay, too.
Anyway,
it seems like this world
is actually connected
to all the mirrors on Whole Cake Island.
I think you, Tia, are right.
So maybe instead of escaping, we should
use Brule's ability to our advantage.
Sounds good, but how?
Since we can see everything, let's
try to locate Sanji That's brilliant!
Great job, Chobro!
That compliment doesn't make me
happy at all, you little scamp you
Secret song, whirlwind slash.
I'd say that we will.
After their patrol route, the
Biscuit warriors go back to the Shit.
We will strike then.
I'll destroy anything that gets
between me and Sanji, no matter what!
Come on, come, come!
Come on, look out!
Time!
Onward!
Honey pretzels!
Good morning, Mama!
We have a very busy day ahead of us.
First on the agenda,
the Vinsmoke family will be stopping
by to attend the engagement ceremony.
Do we have an update on
the wedding cake yet?
That comes tomorrow.
An entire night has passed.
How are those irksome little gnats doing?
They have one last chance
to meet with their Gourmet.
Having some doubts, Mama?
You know they don't stand a
chance against General Cracker.
Once Blackleg steps into this
castle, the deed is as good as done.
Their chance of meeting him is zilch.
After all, the tea party and wedding will
both be held within these very walls.
So they're all talk then, like usual.
We're still waiting on a few
Vinsmokes to arrive, right?
Uh, actually, I've received word
that they just landed at the port.
This is good news indeed.
All of my beloved sons are here.
I cannot wait to see
them face off with Sanji.
Welcome back!
Master Nijiji!
It's been a while!
I can't believe they ended
that long war on rock calling!
Why isn't he coming out to greet us?
Where is he?
Knock it off, Niji.